[{"question":"What is your favorite Olympic event to watch?","answers":["100m Sprint","Gymnastics","Swimming","Soccer","Basketball","Diving","Wrestling","Volleyball"],"categories":["Olympics"]},{"question":"Which country do you think consistently performs the best at the Olympics?","answers":["USA","China","Russia","Germany","Japan","UK","Australia","France"],"categories":["Olympics"]},{"question":"What is your favorite part of the Olympic Games?","answers":["Opening","Competitions","Medals","Closing","Interviews","Moments","Performances","Anthems"],"categories":["Olympics"]},{"question":"Who is your all-time favorite Olympic athlete?","answers":["Usain Bolt","Michael Phelps","Simone Biles","Nadia Comăneci","Carl Lewis","Jesse Owens","Mark Spitz","Allyson Felix"],"categories":["Olympics"]},{"question":"Which Olympic sport do you enjoy the most?","answers":["Track & Field","Swimming","Gymnastics","Soccer","Basketball","Boxing","Tennis","Cycling"],"categories":["Olympics"]},{"question":"Which Olympic performance inspired you the most?","answers":["Bolt’s 100m","Phelps' 8 Golds","Biles' routines","Comăneci's 10","Owens' 4 Golds","Freeman’s 400m","Felix’s relays","Spitz's 7 Golds"],"categories":["Olympics"]},{"question":"How do you show support for your country's athletes during the Olympics?","answers":["Watch live","National colors","Attend events","Social media","Watch parties","Display flags","Share highlights","Online chats"],"categories":["Olympics"]},{"question":"Which Olympic Games had the best opening ceremony?","answers":["Beijing 2008","London 2012","Rio 2016","Tokyo 2020","Sydney 2000","Atlanta 1996","Athens 2004","Barcelona 1992"],"categories":["Olympics"]},{"question":"Which Olympic sport would you love to try?","answers":["Archery","Diving","Fencing","Rowing","Taekwondo","Gymnastics","Cycling","Boxing"],"categories":["Olympics"]},{"question":"Have you ever participated in any Olympic-related events or activities?","answers":["Athlete","Volunteer","Spectator","Training","Fan events","School events"],"categories":["Olympics"]},{"question":"How do you think technology will change the Olympics in the future?","answers":["AR/VR","Athlete Tracking","Fan experiences","Better training","AI officiating","Virtual fans","Safety measures","Smart gear"],"categories":["Olympics"]},{"question":"If you could create your own Olympic sport, what would it be?","answers":["Drone Racing","Tug of War","Dodgeball","Robot Wars","Quidditch","Capture Flag","Endurance Race","Ninja Warrior"],"categories":["Olympics"]},{"question":"What do you think is the most challenging Olympic sport?","answers":["Marathon","Decathlon","Triathlon","Gymnastics","Weightlifting","Swimming","Rowing","Wrestling"],"categories":["Olympics"]}]
